<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.topbraid.lib.jxl.feature"
      label="org.topbraid.lib.jxl.feature"
      version="3.3.2.v20100709-0300R"
      provider-name="TopQuadrant Inc.">

   <description>
      JExcel library and dependent functionality in TopBraid.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      (c) All rights reserved to TopQuadrant, Inc.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      About This Content
March 2010
End User License Agreement
TopQuadrant makes available all content in this Eclipse Feature
(“Content”).
Unless otherwise indicated below, the Content is provided to
you under the terms and conditions of the End User License Agreement
(“EULA”). This EULA sets forth the terms applicable to use and
licensing by the customer (“Customer”) of software provided by
TopQuadrant, Inc. (“TopQuadrant”). It is important that you read
this document before installing or using the software provided
by TopQuadrant (the “Software”) and any associated documentation
or materials provided by TopQuadrant (“Documentation”). A copy
of the EULA is available at http://www.topquadrant.com/docs/legal/EULA.pdf.
If you do not “accept” this EULA on behalf of Customer, then
Customer is not licensed to use the Software, and you must destroy
any downloaded copies of the Software in your or Customer‘s possession
or control. Please go to the TopQuadrant website at http://www.topquadrant.com/docs/legal/EULA.pdf
to download and print a copy of this EULA for your records.
Third Party Content
The Content includes items that have been sourced from third
parties as set out below.
Java Excel API
The plug-in is accompanied by software developed at: http://jexcelapi.sourceforge.net/
The binary code of Java Excel API v2.6.8 (“JExcel”) is included
without modification in the following file(s):
* /org.topbraid.lib.jxl/lib/jxl.jar
Your use of JExcel is subject to the terms and conditions of
the GNU Lesser General Public License (LGPL) published by the
Free Software Foundation. A copy of the license can be found
in /org.topbraid.lib.jxl/about_files/jexcel.LGPL-2.1.txt and is also available at http://www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl-2.1.txt.
The source for the JExcel is included without modification in
the following archive as required by the license terms:
* /org.topbraid.lib.jxl/lib.src/jexcelapi_2_6_8.zip
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="org.topbraid.lib.jxl"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.3.2.v20100709-0300R"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.topbraid.spreadsheets"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.3.2.v20100709-0300R"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.topbraid.tables"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.3.2.v20100709-0300R"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.topbraidcomposer.spreadsheets"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.3.2.v20100709-0300R"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.topbraidcomposer.tables"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.3.2.v20100709-0300R"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
